{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"e-5=","answer":"-2.2817","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"e-pi=","answer":"-0.4232","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"70\u00f761=","answer":"1.1475","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"4-10=","answer":"-6.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"log 10(797)=","answer":"2.9015","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"arithmetic_mixed","question":"sin(-0.5\u03c0)=","answer":"-1.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Math-401"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is the next term in 61, 62, 53, 28, -19?","answer":"-94","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: -75, -80, -85, -90?","answer":"-95","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in -262, -1052, -2360, -4180, -6506, -9332, -12652, -16460?","answer":"-20750","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 1927, 1929, 1929, 1927, 1923?","answer":"1917","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What is next in 44, 39, 32, 23?","answer":"12","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sequence_next_term","question":"What comes next: 97, 178, 259?","answer":"340","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between 813 and -82?","answer":"895.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is -6.5 + -1.5?","answer":"-8.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between -7.077 and -45?","answer":"37.923","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the distance between 0.7 and -1843?","answer":"1843.7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"What is the difference between -54 and -1340?","answer":"1286.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_or_sub","question":"Work out 608.4 + -0.04.","answer":"608.36","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"(-4 - (2 - 3)) + 4","answer":"1.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 2 - (-6 + -2 + 5)?","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 1 - 0 - (-3 - (-1 + 0))?","answer":"3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is the value of (2 - 22) + -1 + 13 + -3?","answer":"-11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"Calculate -4 + 0 - ((-3 - -1) + 7).","answer":"-9","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"add_sub_multiple","question":"What is 7 - (-59 + 65 - (-7 - 0))?","answer":"-6","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -1959 by -1.","answer":"1959","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 0 by 274.","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide -216 by 3.","answer":"-72","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 3 by -1333.","answer":"-3\/1333","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Calculate -238 divided by -3.","answer":"238\/3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div","question":"Divide 360 by -15.","answer":"-24","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"359*92","answer":"33028.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"What is the product of 0.3 and -81?","answer":"-24.3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out -220 * 0.2.","answer":"-44.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Multiply -6 and -0.046.","answer":"0.276","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Multiply -0.0756 and 0.14.","answer":"-0.010584","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"Work out 5 * 354.","answer":"1770.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"108\/(-162)*((-18)\/(-14))\/(-3)","answer":"2\/7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"What is ((7\/(-3))\/7)\/(2\/18)?","answer":"-3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate ((3\/(-1))\/3)\/5.","answer":"-1\/5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate -5*(2\/8)\/(1\/4).","answer":"-5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate 2\/(-6)*(-120)\/(-80).","answer":"-1\/2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul_div_multiple","question":"Evaluate 2\/(2\/(-3))*(-40)\/(-160).","answer":"-3\/4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -17, -4, 3, 14.","answer":"-17, -4, 3, 14","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -52, 2, -4, 3, -5 in descending order.","answer":"3, 2, -4, -5, -52","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -5, 7, 3, -12 in decreasing order.","answer":"7, 3, -5, -12","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 29, 3, -17 in descending order.","answer":"29, 3, -17","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Sort -6, 7, 3, -3.","answer":"-6, -3, 3, 7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put 0, -4, 5, -5, 2 in decreasing order.","answer":"5, 2, 0, -4, -5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many nanoseconds are there in 3505.01 microseconds?","answer":"3505010.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millimeters are there in eleven tenths of a centimeter?","answer":"11","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is three eighths of a kilogram in grams?","answer":"375.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 1183.053 meters in nanometers?","answer":"1183053000000.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"How many millilitres are there in six fifths of a litre?","answer":"1200.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"What is 6.254496 decades in centuries?","answer":"0.6254496","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 4:46 PM and 1:44 AM?","answer":"538","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 583 minutes before 12:57 AM?","answer":"3:14 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"What is 52 minutes before 8:59 PM?","answer":"8:07 PM","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 1:03 PM and 9:11 PM?","answer":"488","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 6:56 PM and 5:27 AM?","answer":"631","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"time","question":"How many minutes are there between 4:09 PM and 3:58 AM?","answer":"709","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 28 is divided by 15?","answer":"13","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"Calculate the remainder when 1088 is divided by 19.","answer":"5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 255 is divided by 20?","answer":"15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 3440 is divided by 855?","answer":"20","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 3495 is divided by 135?","answer":"120","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"div_remainder","question":"What is the remainder when 156 is divided by 57?","answer":"42","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 32 and 20?","answer":"4","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the greatest common divisor of 65 and 1625.","answer":"65","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common divisor of 75 and 390?","answer":"15","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"Calculate the highest common factor of 800 and 325.","answer":"25","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the highest common factor of 26 and 702?","answer":"26","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"gcd","question":"What is the greatest common factor of 17856 and 16?","answer":"16","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the common denominator of -16\/35 and -76\/39.","answer":"1365","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -47\/10 and 19\/681.","answer":"6810","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Calculate the lowest common multiple of 1355 and 80.","answer":"21680","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"Find the common denominator of -4\/57 and 47\/54.","answer":"1026","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the lowest common multiple of 33 and 408?","answer":"4488","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"lcm","question":"What is the smallest common multiple of 24 and 24?","answer":"24","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 18177?","answer":"3, 73, 83","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 118315?","answer":"5, 23663","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 17064.","answer":"2, 3, 79","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 10563?","answer":"3, 7, 503","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"List the prime factors of 1125.","answer":"3, 5","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 10396?","answer":"2, 23, 113","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 289?","answer":"8","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 5546?","answer":"4.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 804?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the hundreds digit of 3248?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the tens digit of 29409?","answer":"0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"place_value","question":"What is the units digit of 232?","answer":"2","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.000001115 rounded to seven dps?","answer":"1.1e-06","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is 0.11795 rounded to 3 decimal places?","answer":"0.118","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -0.27868 rounded to two decimal places?","answer":"-0.28","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round 4117.6 to the nearest 10.","answer":"4120.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"What is -892.7 rounded to the nearest 10?","answer":"-890.0","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"round_number","question":"Round -0.035847 to two dps.","answer":"-0.04","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"conversion","question":"Convert 5.92509 litres to millilitres.","answer":"5925.09","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"list_prime_factors","question":"What are the prime factors of 50103?","answer":"3, 19, 293","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"sort","question":"Put -24\/13, 0.4, -3, 2\/3 in descending order.","answer":"2\/3, 0.4, -24\/13, -3","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
{"category":"Arithmetic","subcategory":"mul","question":"2.9 times 13","answer":"37.7","reasoning":null,"source":"Mathematics Dataset (Google DeepMind)"}
